Formerly Welcome to Ludhiana from Punjab
Miss you are turmeric Happy and moving towards
achieving goals in recent days
In this video Guava describes something important specific
for international
students Coming and planning commission came during the
period of time Now this is over
friends this new one is coming So keeping this in
mind we are going to make this
video on Chashma in this video we will use both
Hindi and English languages ​​Being that
most of my viewers are
Hindi you are referring to the
software Just meeting this video
calling to date and will provide you all the important
information to all your guidance
and it's really important when you are
coming to Canada this is a good
positive at airport rider customers tweet
result you get a positive fog So
unfortunately what is going to happen is that
your health insurance is going to cover this
Your university's habit insurance will
cover it  Whether this situation will be resolved or not,
we are going to talk about all these things
and this is a very important
issue, the issue is not that you are getting a
flight ticket, the
next flight is being booked,
I am about to reach and what you have to do,
what is going to happen after that,
you have to think that two three
steps which are dangerous in the sense that
anything can happen,
you are coming right up in line and even I just
read an article in which it was written that the
chances of Omicron spreading are
much higher than 200,
please watch this video to Ladakh and Wicked
Aangan to provide you all of the information in the
next video solid solid
[music]
so stop here first I am going to start with
what is health insurance
and why is it important now I have a channel
on YouTube called Party Wear,
I know that stock futures and I
also follow its videos  You must be watching this
promotional video, this is my honest
review that he makes very good videos, so in that
he shared an incident
that a person came and he got into the development
system, then the government here gave
him an appointment immediately
in the comment hospital, now he is not able to understand
that this is increasing in Delhi
and when the cases reached 4258 then he
felt that yes now it is fine, then the doctor felt that he
blew him away for
9000, can you imagine that, so in a very formal manner, what should
I do now,
he talked to his parents that science becomes
very high, our college
fees are increased by 1000, right, so
what happened after that, Lakshmi, she had taken travel
insurance, due to which half of her
Mount Abu trip was completed, but the half
Mount will have to be covered, now such a
situation should not happen with you people, then it is
really important to have a travel
insurance, I don't know how much money is required for that travel, but I am  I'm
going to provide you with one
website, the description box is the
last of the dips, rate.com. In this,
you will get insurance quotes,
after paying how much, what
coverage are you going to get, coverage in the sense,
which medical things are going to be covered in it, what will be
their price,
right, you will get to know everything about those things
in that website, so I am
also giving its link in the description box
and I am really cheating, I am not going to get any money,
this is just a promotion,
but now let's tell the truth,
you people should know this thing, it is important that even
when I came, I
also did not know about this, nothing like this happened, it is not fake,
but if something like this had happened, then
how would I have survived, so
please keep this thing in mind, right,
travel insurance is important, whenever you are
booking, if it seems to be
23 thousand rupees more for you, then that's okay, but you can
go comfortably, right, you are not going to be afraid, so the
first thing is this, after that
I have some covers  Now that you come here, there are
some provinces
that help you provide health
insurance, but whenever you're going to start
paying
premiums, and sometimes there are some problems
like the
health insurance isn't provided to international students, so what are the
added conditions, what will you have to do
about that as well? We'll discuss that as well. There are
some universities and colleges
that will provide you insurance. So, what are the
insurance fees,
what is its structure, how does it
work, what coverage is there on it,
and
mostly I'm going to take
Electronic Polytechnic
University as an example.
All the universities and colleges in British Columbia
work in the same way,
we'll discuss that. So, even before we
start with that, okay, now we'll
discuss that. Thakur, you'll take travel insurance.
Now, when you come here,
some of your universities and colleges, what do they do
when your tuition
fee structure is fixed?  When you prepare it,
they transfer your health insurance
money there. Now, there are many
students who do not know about these things
and we do not even take advantage of it.
For example, we are here, Ayat. Now, like
recently, it happened with me. One day, blood started
appearing. So what did I do? My
workmates told me that they had experience
but they knew everything. So, they told me
that you should go to this clinic and get a checkup done. So,
I went to a private clinic and got
myself checked there. They charged me
$60 just to check my 22nd eye side.
They charged me $60 because you have
presented the bill. I have done it like this. I have mentioned the credit
card in it. So, I said okay. I did it.
I came home and checked my email. I
mailed to the health insurance people who provide it behind us. I
told them to settle me here. There is
a website with a dot me in it which
works with PU which
provides insurance to students and we do
not even know that in our every sector
2002  $30 is going towards medical benefits,
which we're not even using.
Now, I'm going to explain how to
increase your savings.
We're also going to talk about that. Okay, so this is a done
deal. If I forget about it,
they just did it for me. I
gave them my bank account information. It was
sent to my bank account and it came back from there. So, in
this way, you can take advantage of your health
insurance, which your
college friends are taking.
We don't know anything about this.
Right, and I'm going to talk about it in detail. The
video may be a little long,
but do watch it. Pictures are important. There's a
lot of
information that I didn't even know myself. So, if
you come to International Space
International Powder here, there are a
lot of problems here. I've
opened a website there. If
you also show Reddy, I've
explained the different rules there. Now, for example,
in Alberta, public health insurance is available, and the
eligibility for it is that you  You
must be in Canada for six months, after which
you can start the Alberta Health Care Insurance Plan.
You will incur a
premium cost. There are light monthly
withdrawals, and its range. If we talk about its cost, it starts
at $2 from the left parties. The
total withdrawal is from $1, which
means your monthly cost is between 16 and 17
times. Now, if we
talk about British Columbia, the medical
insurance amount for this plan is
$75 monthly. There are students here who,
without paying, think that
maybe they will be able to complete
their subjects. Right, but that's not going to happen. The $
75 issue will not go into the
details about this plan. If
you can pay it yourself, then if you
do an extension of your
studies, then you will have to make a
deduction for that, right, then the
relief amount that you pay $75 will have on your credit score. I think that will have a
significant impact on your credit score as well. Now, let's talk about what a credit score is.
In this case,
just understand that yes, we will do
something about it, then after that, British Columbia, which
I told you, is called MSP here, now
I told Praveen how is Ontario
AC, which does not
provide medical insurance to international students, even
if you want it on premium, Devraj,
it is not going to provide you any free medical coverage
and you know that the
medical coverage in Canada is
very expensive, it
costs a lot to see a doctor here, so that is why
this insurance
is very important for us because if we have this
insurance, then we
can book our appointment with any doctor, we
can meet with any doctor and the doctor
can subscribe us for free, for the
cost of medicine,
we will have to pay its office bill, but here we will
not have to pay the office bill for seeing the doctor, so this is the real
benefit, okay, so now New Brix, well,
Newfoundland and Nova Scotia, so
all this is included in it,
I am also placed according to a screenshot, so
I am adding this screenshot here
in the description box.  So that you can
read about this and you will know
which one provides Pravin
and which one does not and you will have to be prepared for the recording
and now let us come to the
next thing that is why
PU is doing this, it is its work with dot me through
which they
deduct 275 of our fees and 215 followers from our financial year semester wise so
what happens in that, they have given that thing a
name, you can still check your
PU students
through the website ss.com, send there,
after adding, there is my tuition fee, that good
chart comes out, right, like the
complete one for Spring 2022 will come out, then look in it,
there will definitely be a column for
Kaya's PIO temporary medical insurance
and two 200-250 college kids will have come out and
we do not take advantage of it when we need it, it is
important to check it for a while, it will
come up, placing one
screenshot here can you please read and  Now
look here Irom told that the
cost of the full semester is 2017 quantum
alarms and you can fit it now I am going to
tell you how you can save money
now you have the channel right now you have
Chinu's insurance so let's go right
when your two to three months are over you are
eligible to apply for MS PM SP
first put it on flight mode one feels like having
fun right so when
you have applied I got this piece free of
cost in the meantime go and like
in ICC literature so after applying there
you get a policy has number
PHN that is the hand number of chemistry
now when you get the MSP card they will
send an email to your phone that I
have MSP and its health number
is 10 so I have to take more money from this temporary
insurance policy of yours medical
so when you write this
you provide them proof that
you have MSP then they will give you up
means data on their respective  There were $2 extra that was
going to you, which you were not even
taking advantage of, which you were not even aware of, that was for
your child. Now the sooner you
come to Canada, the sooner you like the difficult MSP here,
the sooner your 2018 will be from there,
whether the former PM SP of the land gap is gone,
right next month, so that's why keep
this thing in mind, I also
understood it very late, the hunter of the last semester, the ones
before that were saved,
I know a little bit, well, this also happens, that's why
I am telling you all this, keep in
mind all these things, there is
also an extended policy, there is an
extended airplane in which dental
colleges are covered, you
can also do this, this e want and in this I think in this there is
$25 for health and 110 for your stalk, so whatever the
total amount goes according to the hair on Mount Abu, then
you can top up,
this eighth soil, it has some
deadlines, I am giving the link
of the pdf file like in a description box
there  In which there
is complete coverage about health insurance, it is
also told in it that how you have to
remember and which things are
covered and for how much month, what you have to do or
not, so now if you are a student of 12th year then you
must read that file,
Ride Ashok, this is all for this video, I
hope that you must have collected the information from this video
and please subscribe
this channel Punjabi Ke Needs and liked this
video and share with your friends,
I know that I am not regular
in making videos and a mix lover, sorry for this, but
whatever information you are seeing is
correct, you can reply after that,
search whenever you come,
take advantage of this thing, whatever you want because we ourselves do not
know that we are doing all this, right, we are
testing so many things and doing those people, so
thanks for watching this video, thank you so much, it was